Hirsh Health Sciences Library Records UA225
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Hirsh Health Sciences Library Records
1893 -- 2013
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Hirsh, Jane
Hirsh Health Sciences Library
UA225
10.33 Linear Feet 15 boxes
1066 Digital Object(s)
Arrangement
The collection is organized into five series: Grant Files; Team and Committee Minutes and Notes; Administrative Files; Slide Library; and Additional Accessions.
Custodial History
Initial transfer of materials for this collection consisted on 10 boxes from Cora Ho, Deputy Director of the Hirsh Health Sciences Library until December, 2011. Files included her own papers as well as the papers of previous directors and the library as a whole.
Scope and Contents
The collection contains grant files, correspondence, memoranda, announcements, flyers, minutes, annual reports, library statistics, budget survey, and other administrative files, from 1924 to 2010. It also includes electronic files originally stored in several different types of media of which 3 1⁄2-inch floppy disks and 5 1/2-inch floppy disks are dominant. Additionally, there are a few VHS tapes, audio cassettes, CDs, and a DLTtape. The bulk of the materials was created and compiled by the Directors and Deputy Directors of the Library, such as Elizabeth Eaton and Cora Ho, from the mid-1980s to the 2000s. The records also include materials created prior to the official founding of a separate health sciences library at Tufts, as well as materials that pre-date the establishment of the Hirsh Health Sciences Library in 2005.
Biographical / Historical
The Health Scienes Library (2005-) was opened in 2005 with a donation from pharmaceutical CEO Jane Hirsh and named in honor of her, her husband Dr. Mark Hirsh (DG68), and her two children, who also graduated from Tufts University.
The library is located on the fourth floor of the Tufts Center for Medical Education building, formerly the Arthur M. Sackler Center for Health Communications, and is administered by the Tufts University Medical School. The library's collections support education for Tufts University's School of Medicine, School of Dental Medicine, Friedman School of Nutrition Science and Policy, Tufts New England Medical Center, and Tufts Graduate School of Biomedical Sciences. Eric Albright has been the library's director since its opening in April 2005.
Conditions Governing Access
This collection contains some restricted material. Restrictions related to specific material are listed in the detailed contents list. This collection may require review before it is available for use. Please contact DCA for further details.
Academic Support -- Libraries, Galleries, Archives; Advancement
- Grant Files, 1982 -- 2001; UA225.001; 2.4 Linear Feet; 1 Digital Object(s)
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains grant applications, project proposals, evaluations, and other related documents on behalf of the Hirsh Health Sciences Library and its predecessor library on the Tufts Boston Campus. A large portion of files are associated with programs from National Science Foundation (NSF) and National Library of Medicine (NLM). The bulk of the documents were created in the 1990s.
  Arrangement
  This series was arranged in the order it was received.
  Conditions Governing Access
  20 years from date of creation.
  - National Presentation Program for The Biomedical Literature, 1990/1991 [1 of 2], 1989 -- 1991; UA225.001.001.00001 (Box 1)
  - National Presentation Program for The Biomedical Literature, 1990/1991 [2 of 2], 1983 -- 1991; UA225.001.001.00002 (Box 1)
  - FOGARTY - 1999 South Africa, 1998 -- 1999; UA225.001.001.00003 (Box 1)
  - Primary Care Program - Remote Information Services Seminar, 1995 -- 1997; UA225.001.001.00004 (Box 1)
  - HSDB - Evaluation Form Results, 1995 -- 1998; UA225.001.001.00005 (Box 1)
  - NNILM ID# 512395 5-1-95 to 4-30-94 Urban Outreach Project, 1993 -- 1999; UA225.001.001.00006 (Box 1)
  - NSFNET, 1993 -- 1994; UA225.001.001.00007 (Box 1)
  - 2001 NLM Associate Final Application, UA225.001.001.00008 (Box 1)
    - NLM Associate Fellow Grant, 2001; UA225.001.001.00008.00001
  - HSL Grant Applications and Program in Medical Information Sciences Report, 1995 -- 2000; UA225.001.001.00009 (Box 1)
  - Preceptor Project, 1993 -- 1996; UA225.001.001.00010 (Box 1)
  - General Practice Preceptors, 1993 -- 1997; UA225.001.001.00011 (Box 1)
  - Preceptor Project Reports, 1995 -- 2000; UA225.001.001.00012 (Box 1)
  - General Practice Program - Active File, 1995; UA225.001.001.00013 (Box 1)
  - IAIMS Grant [Binder], 1991 -- 1994; UA225.001.001.00014 (Box 1)
  - IAIMS Grant 1985 [Binder], 1982 -- 1985; UA225.001.001.00015 (Box 1)
  - IAIMS Planning Grant, 1991 -- 1993; UA225.001.001.00016 (Box 1)
  - Tufts MLM-IAIMS Pink Sheets, 1993; UA225.001.001.00017 (Box 1)
  - IAIMS Application Complete, 1993; UA225.001.001.00018 (Box 1)
  - IAIMS PLAW - Draft, 1993; UA225.001.001.00019 (Box 1)
  - XTRA-IAIMS Agenda and Site Visit, 1992 -- 1993; UA225.001.001.00020 (Box 1)
  - NSF/NCM Grant, 1993; UA225.001.001.00021 (Box 1)
  - NLM - Resubmission, Copy 2 for HSL, 1999 -- 2000; UA225.001.001.00022 (Box 1)
  - NLM Continuation Supporting Document/drops etc., 1997 -- 1999; UA225.001.001.00023 (Box 1)
  - HSL HSDB G08 LM05774-03A1, 1999 -- 2000; UA225.001.001.00024 (Box 1)
  - NSF D2L, 1998 -- 1999; UA225.001.002.00001 (Box UA225 Shared 1)
  - NBME Grant, 1998; UA225.001.002.00002 (Box UA225 Shared 1)
  - US DEPT EDUC - Grant Application, 1993 -- 1994; UA225.001.002.00003 (Box UA225 Shared 1)
  - NLM/IMAGE I, 1992 -- 1995; UA225.001.002.00004 (Box UA225 Shared 1)
  - NLM/IMAGE II, 1995 -- 1996; UA225.001.002.00005 (Box UA225 Shared 1)
  - NLM/IMAGE III, 1996; UA225.001.002.00006 (Box UA225 Shared 1)
  - DLI-2 IIS-9817517, 1999; UA225.001.002.00007 (Box UA225 Shared 1)
  - NLM Second Year Associate Fellowship Proposal, 2000 -- 2001; UA225.001.002.00008 (Box UA225 Shared 1)
  - NLM-N01-LM-0-3519 National Preservation Program for the Biomedical Literature, 1990; UA225.001.002.00009 (Box UA225 Shared 1)
  - Dental Curriculum Grant, 1994; UA225.001.002.00010 (Box UA225 Shared 1)
  - SPIRAL grant files, 2003 June 15 -- 2011 May 24; UA225.001306; 10.2 Megabytes One .zip file comprised of four files.
    Final reports from SPIRAL: Selected Patient Information Resources in Asian Languages, a grant-funded project from the New England Region of the National Network of Libraries of Medicine under contract N01-LM-6-3508.
    Immediate Source of Acquisition
    Transferred by Amy LaVertu, Research and Instruction Librarian, Hirsch Health Sciences Library, in November 2019, accession number UA-2020-032.
- Team and Committee minutes and notes, 1976 -- 2010; UA225.002; 2.4 Linear Feet; 2 Digital Object(s)
  This series contains meeting minutes, memoranda, correspondence and budget files mostly pertaining to Health Science Library cabinet meetings, staff meetings, and committee meetings. The bulk of the files was created between 1980 and 2000.
  This series is arranged chronologically within meeting type.
  - Cabinet Meeting Notes [Binder 1 of 2], 1986 -- 1987; UA225.002.002.00011 (Box UA225 Shared 1)
  - Cabinet Meeting Notes [Binder 2 of 2], 1987 -- 1988; UA225.002.002.00012 (Box UA225 Shared 1)
  - Cabinet Meeting Notes 1991- [Binder 1 of 3], 1991 -- 1993; UA225.002.002.00013 (Box UA225 Shared 1)
  - Cabinet Meeting Notes 1991- [Binder 2 of 3], 1991 -- 1993; UA225.002.002.00014 (Box UA225 Shared 1)
  - Cabinet Meeting Notes 1991- [Binder 3 of 3], UA225.002.002.00015 (Box UA225 Shared 1)
  - Cabinet 1994/95 [Binder 1 of 2], 1994 -- 1996; UA225.002.002.00016 (Box UA225 Shared 1)
  - Cabinet 1994/95 [Binder 2 of 2], 1993 -- 1994; UA225.002.002.00017 (Box UA225 Shared 1)
  - Cabinet 98-Sept 99 and Sept 99-Sept 2000 [Binder], 1997 -- 2001; UA225.002.003.00001 (Box UA225 Shared 2)
  - Health Sciences Library Committee 1996/1998 1999/2000 [Binder 1 of 2], 1998 -- 2001; UA225.002.003.00002 (Box UA225 Shared 2)
  - Health Sciences Library Committee 1996/1998 1999/2000 [Binder 2 of 2], 1995 -- 1998; UA225.002.003.00003 (Box UA225 Shared 2)
  - HSL Archives, 1976 -- 1977; UA225.002.003.00004 (Box UA225 Shared 2)
  - Staff Meetings, 1985 -- 1990; UA225.002.003.00005 (Box UA225 Shared 2)
  - Tufts Affiliated Hospitals Librarians Meeting, 1988; UA225.002.003.00006 (Box UA225 Shared 2)
  - Letter heads, 1980 -- 2010; UA225.002.003.00007 (Box UA225 Shared 2)
  - Student Library Advisory Committee Minute [Binder], 1984 -- 2005; UA225.002.003.00008 (Box UA225 Shared 2)
  - Health Sciences Library Budgets [Binder 1 of 2], 2002 -- 2004; UA225.002.003.00009 (Box UA225 Shared 2)
  - Health Sciences Library Budgets [Binder 2 of 2], 1999 -- 2003; UA225.002.003.00010 (Box UA225 Shared 2)
  - FY00/01 [Binder 1 of 2], 2001 -- 2002; UA225.002.003.00011 (Box UA225 Shared 2)
    - HSL and IR Committee Meeting, 2002; UA225.002.003.00011.00001
    - Wireless - memo and forms, 2001; UA225.002.003.00011.00002
  - FY00/01 [Binder 2 of 2], 2000; UA225.002.003.00012 (Box UA225 Shared 2)
- Administrative Files, 1924 -- 2013; UA225.003; 7.75 Linear Feet; 34 Digital Object(s)
  This series contains various administrative files including surveys, annual reports, statistics, budget proposals, memoranda, correspondence, flyers, personal certificates, newsletters, journals, and the Hirsh Health Sciences Library disaster plan and policies. The series contains physical materials as well as a large number of digital files that were originally housed on a wide variety of portable media. The bulk of the materials was created from the 1990s to the 2000s.
  This series is arranged as received with electronic files cataloged at the end of the physical materials unless they were interfiled.
  20 years from date of creation. Open for research.
  - Reports and Dianne Schmoyer files, 1973 -- 1987; UA225.003.003.00013; Eaton, Elizabeth (Box UA225 Shared 2)
  - Curriculum Committee - Dental, 1978 -- 1981; UA225.003.003.00014; Eaton, Elizabeth (Box UA225 Shared 2)
  - Faculty Committees, 1979 -- 1982; UA225.003.003.00015; Eaton, Elizabeth (Box UA225 Shared 2)
  - Annual Reports, 1932 -- 1981; UA225.003.003.00016; Eaton, Elizabeth (Box UA225 Shared 2)
  - Learning Resources Committee, 1971 -- 1981; UA225.003.003.00017; Eaton, Elizabeth (Box UA225 Shared 2)
  - Nutrition, 1976; UA225.003.003.00018; Eaton, Elizabeth (Box UA225 Shared 2)
  - Primary Library Users, 1982; UA225.003.003.00019; Eaton, Elizabeth (Box UA225 Shared 2)
  - Association of Academic Health Sciences Library Directors, 1978 -- 1982; UA225.003.003.00020; Eaton, Elizabeth (Box UA225 Shared 2)
  - Basic Science Journals [1 of 3], 1980; UA225.003.004.00001; Eaton, Elizabeth (Box 4)
  - Basic Science Journals [2 of 3], 1980; UA225.003.004.00002; Eaton, Elizabeth (Box 4)
  - Basic Science Journals [3 of 3], 1980; UA225.003.004.00003; Eaton, Elizabeth (Box 4)
  - Ex: Info Services Librarians, Janet Holborow, Linda VanHorn, Brynn Mays, 1992 -- 2001; UA225.003.004.00004; Eaton, Elizabeth (Box 4)
  - Maine Contract - Dental School, 1972; UA225.003.004.00005; Eaton, Elizabeth (Box 4)
  - Memorandum, 1994 -- 1995; UA225.003.004.00006; Eaton, Elizabeth (Box 4)
  - Tufts University Learning Resource Center [Binder], 1999; UA225.003.004.00007; Eaton, Elizabeth (Box 4)
  - Boston Medical Library, 1989; UA225.003.004.00008; Eaton, Elizabeth (Box 4)
  - Accreditation, Medical School, 1981 -- 1986; UA225.003.004.00009; Eaton, Elizabeth (Box 4)
  - Accreditation, Medical School, 1983 -- 1985; UA225.003.004.00010; Eaton, Elizabeth (Box 4)
  - May 1998 Corchrane Clinical Care Research Dr. Lau, UA225.003.004.00011; Eaton, Elizabeth (Box 4)
  - Memorandum, 1999 -- 2001; UA225.003.004.00012; Eaton, Elizabeth (Box 4)
  - Misc. Administ. Incoming [Binder], 2000 -- 2001; UA225.003.004.00013; Eaton, Elizabeth (Box 4)
  - Sakler School, 1983 -- 1986; UA225.003.004.00014; Eaton, Elizabeth (Box 4)
  - HNRC Serials, 1990; UA225.003.004.00015; Eaton, Elizabeth (Box 4)
  - Serial Conversions, 1985 -- 1986; UA225.003.004.00016; Eaton, Elizabeth (Box 4)
  - Serials Survey, 1990; UA225.003.004.00017; Eaton, Elizabeth (Box 4)
  - OCLC, 1983 -- 1991; UA225.003.004.00018; Eaton, Elizabeth (Box 4)
  - NN/LM, TCLL and Boston Library Consortium, 1993 -- 1999; UA225.003.004.00019; Eaton, Elizabeth (Box 4)
  - Clinical Teleconference Program, 1992 -- 1997; UA225.003.004.00020; Eaton, Elizabeth (Box 4)
  - HSL, 1986; UA225.003.004.00021; Eaton, Elizabeth (Box 4)
  - Exit Survey, 1995; UA225.003.004.00022; Eaton, Elizabeth (Box 4)
  - Tufts Health Sciences Library NMAC Satellite Collection, 1986; UA225.003.004.00023; Eaton, Elizabeth (Box 4)
  - Media Catalog, 1983; UA225.003.004.00024; Eaton, Elizabeth (Box 4)
  - Vali-Dine, 1988 -- 1999; UA225.003.004.00025; Eaton, Elizabeth (Box 4)
  - COPICO, 1993 -- 1994; UA225.003.004.00026; Eaton, Elizabeth (Box 4)
  - Computer Lease - April 99, 1999 -- 2001; UA225.003.004.00027; Eaton, Elizabeth (Box 4)
  - Development THSL, 1986 -- 1987; UA225.003.004.00028; Eaton, Elizabeth (Box 4)
  - Computer Lab Survey and Tufts I.D. Packet, 1998 -- 1999; UA225.003.004.00029; Eaton, Elizabeth (Box 4)
  - P.R. Account# 234032, 1985 -- 1991; UA225.003.004.00030; Eaton, Elizabeth (Box 4)
  - 1995-1997 Ovid Finance, 1995 -- 1999; UA225.003.004.00031; Eaton, Elizabeth (Box 4)
  - Centennial-1993 Tufts-Med, 1988 -- 1992; UA225.003.004.00032; Eaton, Elizabeth (Box 4)
  - 1999 Learning Resource Center Computer Lab Patron Survey, Administration Copy, UA225.003.004.00033; Eaton, Elizabeth (Box 4)
  - Correspondence, 1984 -- 2001; UA225.003.005.00001; Eaton, Elizabeth (Box 5)
  - Certificates, 1986 -- 1999; UA225.003.005.00002; Eaton, Elizabeth (Box 5)
  - Liz Eaton-Personal File, 1983; UA225.003.005.00003; Eaton, Elizabeth (Box 5)
  - Personnel, 1982 -- 2001; UA225.003.005.00004; Eaton, Elizabeth (Box 5)
  - Jane Hirsh-Tufts Women's Initiative, 1999; UA225.003.005.00005; Eaton, Elizabeth (Box 5)
  - 1993-1994 Arts and Sciences Library User Survey, UA225.003.005.00006; Eaton, Elizabeth (Box 5)
  - Cora Ho - Countway Library of Medicine and HSL, 1982 -- 1989; UA225.003.005.00007; Ho, Cora (Box 5)
  - 30th Annual Survey, 2001 -- 2008; UA225.003.005.00008; Ho, Cora (Box 5)
  - Nutrition, 2001 -- 2002; UA225.003.005.00009; Ho, Cora (Box 5)
  - Chinese Health Fair Subcommittee, 2004 -- 2005; UA225.003.005.00010; Ho, Cora (Box 5)
  - Survey, Budget proposal, Annual reports etc., 1999 -- 2008; UA225.003.005.00011; Ho, Cora (Box 5)
  - Library Expenses FY0708, 2008; UA225.003.005.00012; Ho, Cora (Box 5)
  - Financial Report, 2007 -- 2008; UA225.003.005.00013; Ho, Cora (Box 4)
  - Annual Statistics, 2008; UA225.003.005.00014; Ho, Cora (Box 5)
  - Budget Meeting, 2006 -- 2007; UA225.003.005.00015; Ho, Cora (Box 5)
  - Annual Reports, 1995 -- 2008; UA225.003.005.00016; Ho, Cora (Box 5)
  - HSL Memorandum, flyers, and newsletters, 1986 -- 2011; UA225.003.005.00017; Ho, Cora (Box 5)
  - HSL Services Manual, 1990 -- 2002; UA225.003.005.00018; Ho, Cora (Box 5)
  - Archives, Medical Sackler, 1996; UA225.003.005.00019; Ho, Cora (Box 5)
  - Dean Harrington, 1994 -- 1998; UA225.003.005.00020; Ho, Cora (Box 5)
  - Cora Ho's Correspondence [1 of 2], 1981 -- 1984; UA225.003.005.00021; Ho, Cora (Box 5)
  - Cora Ho's Correspondence [2 of 2], 1978 -- 1985; UA225.003.005.00022; Ho, Cora (Box 5)
  - NEMC, 1983 -- 1986; UA225.003.005.00023; Ho, Cora (Box 5)
  - E-journal - HSL for Study and Cancellation, 1991 -- 1999; UA225.003.005.00024; Ho, Cora (Box 5)
  - Facilities, Policies, and Services brochure, 1986; UA225.003.005.00025
  - CD PLUS Financial Group, 1993 -- 1996; UA225.003.006.00001; Ho, Cora (Box 6)
  - Fair Use Subcommittee - Mary Lee Jacobs, 1999 -- 2001; UA225.003.006.00002; Ho, Cora (Box 6)
  - Fair Use FAQs Copyright, 2001; UA225.003.006.00003; Ho, Cora (Box 6)
  - Budget, 1992 -- 1998; UA225.003.006.00004; Eaton, Elizabeth (Box 6)
  - P.R., 1986 -- 1995; UA225.003.006.00005; Eaton, Elizabeth (Box 6)
  - DOCLINE, 1985; UA225.003.006.00006; Eaton, Elizabeth (Box 6)
  - HHSL Disaster Plan, 1981 -- 1991; UA225.003.006.00007; Ho, Cora (Box 6)
  - HHSL Policy, 1981 -- 2002; UA225.003.006.00008; Ho, Cora (Box 6)
  - AAHSLD Annual Statistics 18th edition, 1994 -- 1995; UA225.003.006.00009
  - Spreadsheet files, 1994; UA225.003.006.00010
  - 22nd AAHSL Survey, 1998 -- 1999; UA225.003.006.00011
  - BLC Salary Survey, 1999 -- 2003; UA225.003.006.00012
  - BLC Salary Survey, 2000 -- 2001; UA225.003.006.00013
  - AAHSL Statistics FY2006/2007 [Binder 1 of 4], 2001 -- 2006; UA225.003.006.00014; Ho, Cora (Box 6)
  - AAHSL Statistics FY2006/2007 [Binder 2 of 4], 1992 -- 2000; UA225.003.006.00015; Ho, Cora (Box 6)
  - AAHSL Statistics FY2006/2007 [Binder 3 of 4], 1989 -- 2002; UA225.003.006.00016; Ho, Cora (Box 6)
  - AAHSL Statistics FY2006/2007 [Binder 4 of 4], 1983 -- 2003; UA225.003.006.00017; Ho, Cora (Box 6)
  - Memorandum [Binder 1 of 2], 1984 -- 2000; UA225.003.006.00018; Ho, Cora (Box 6)
  - Memorandum [Binder 2 of 2], 1983 -- 1999; UA225.003.006.00019; Ho, Cora (Box 6)
  - Factbook [Binder 1 of 2], 1990 -- 2005; UA225.003.006.00020; Ho, Cora (Box 6)
  - Factbook [Binder 2 of 2], 1990 -- 2002; UA225.003.006.00021; Ho, Cora (Box 6)
  - Library Statistics [Binder], 1993 -- 2002; UA225.003.007.00001; Ho, Cora (Box 7)
  - AAHSL Survey, 1999 -- 2006; UA225.003.007.00002; Ho, Cora (Box 7)
  - Circulation, 1983 -- 1986; UA225.003.007.00003; Ho, Cora (Box 7)
  - Library Statistics [Binder], 1983 -- 1999; UA225.003.007.00004; Ho, Cora (Box 7)
  - HSL Goals for 2004, 2003; UA225.003.007.00005; Ho, Cora (Box 7)
  - Survey, 1980 -- 1984; UA225.003.007.00006; Ho, Cora (Box 7)
  - A note of librarian's annual reports with gaps 1924-1980, UA225.003.007.00007; Ho, Cora (Box 7)
  - Tufts-NEMC - JCAHO (April 2005), UA225.003.007.00008; Ho, Cora (Box 7)
  - HSL Annual Report FY-2001-02, 2002; UA225.003.007.00009; Ho, Cora (Box 7)
  - Wireless Computing Pilot Study, 2002; UA225.003.007.00010; Ho, Cora (Box 7)
  - Legal documents, 1993 -- 2000; UA225.003.007.00011; Ho, Cora (Box 7)
  - 2000 Library Stats Uses etc, UA225.003.007.00012; Ho, Cora (Box 7)
  - Ref Annual Report, 1995 -- 1997; UA225.003.007.00013; Ho, Cora (Box 7)
  - Budget [Binder], 1990 -- 1994; UA225.003.007.00014; Ho, Cora (Box 7)
  - Library Expenses, 1924 -- 1960; UA225.003.007.00015; Ho, Cora (Box 7)
  - Annual Reports, 1960 -- 1970; UA225.003.007.00016; Ho, Cora (Box 7)
  - Annual Reports, 1971 -- 1980; UA225.003.007.00017; Ho, Cora (Box 7)
  - Board of Visitors Tufts University Libraries, 1971 -- 1976; UA225.003.007.00018; Ho, Cora (Box 7)
  - Extra Copiers for Archives, 1970 -- 1974; UA225.003.007.00019; Ho, Cora (Box 7)
  - Annual Reports, 1980 -- 1981; UA225.003.007.00020; Ho, Cora (Box 7)
  - Annual Report, 1981 -- 1982; UA225.003.007.00021; Ho, Cora (Box 7)
  - Annual Reports 83-84, 1984 -- 1986; UA225.003.007.00022; Ho, Cora (Box 7)
  - Annual Report, 1982 -- 1983; UA225.003.007.00023; Ho, Cora (Box 7)
  - Annual Report 1983/84, 1983 -- 1988; UA225.003.007.00024; Ho, Cora (Box 7)
    Consists of Job Performance Evaluation 19983/84 and Budget Request 83-84
  - Annual Report 1984/85 [1 of 2], 1984 -- 1985; UA225.003.008.00001; Ho, Cora (Box 8)
  - Annual Report 1984/85 [2 of 2], 1983 -- 1985; UA225.003.008.00002; Ho, Cora (Box 8)
  - Annual report 1985/86 [1 of 2], 1986; UA225.003.008.00003; Ho, Cora (Box 8)
  - Annual report 1985/86 [2 of 2], 1983 -- 1987; UA225.003.008.00004; Ho, Cora (Box 8)
  - Annual Report 1986/87 [1 of 2], 1984 -- 1987; UA225.003.008.00005; Ho, Cora (Box 8)
  - Annual Report 1986/87 [2 of 2], 1987; UA225.003.008.00006; Ho, Cora (Box 8)
  - Annual Report 1987/88 [1 of 2], 1987 -- 1988; UA225.003.008.00007; Ho, Cora (Box 8)
  - Annual Report 1987/88 [2 of 2], 1987 -- 1988; UA225.003.008.00008; Ho, Cora (Box 8)
  - Budget 1988/1989 and Background [1 of 2], 1988 -- 1991; UA225.003.008.00009; Ho, Cora (Box 8)
  - Budget 1988/1989 and Background [2 of 2], 1989 -- 1992; UA225.003.008.00010; Ho, Cora (Box 8)
    - AR8990 WP A:PRCOMM, 1990 -- 1992; UA225.003.008.00010.00001
    - 1A WP-99, 1990 -- 1991; UA225.003.008.00010.00002
    - WORDSTAR #3 COLLDEV.DOC, 1989 -- 1990; UA225.003.008.00010.00003
  - Budget 1990/91, 1980 -- 1991; UA225.003.008.00011; Ho, Cora (Box 8)
    - WP5.1 LRC-1991, LRCCHART.TC, UA225.003.008.00011.00001
    - Information Services Annual Report WS2, 1990 -- 1991; UA225.003.008.00011.00002
    - EC (WP) Annrept (Q)Circ8990.wk1, (Q)User8990.wkq, (Q)RPRT8990.wk1, 1980 -- 1990; UA225.003.008.00011.00003
  - Annual Report 1991/92, 1990 -- 1992; UA225.003.008.00012; Ho, Cora (Box 8)
    - SLIDEWRITE India Slide, 1990 -- 1991; UA225.003.008.00012.00001
    - EEHTON-Library SUP: Slide, 1990; UA225.003.008.00012.00002
    - profact.ejr, info92.rpt, 1991 -- 1992; UA225.003.008.00012.00003
  - Budget 1992/93, 1991; UA225.003.008.00013; Ho, Cora (Box 8)
  - Annual Report 1992/93, UA225.003.008.00014; Ho, Cora (Box 8)
  - Budget Request 93/94, 1992; UA225.003.008.00015; Ho, Cora (Box 8)
  - Annual Report 1993/94, 1994; UA225.003.008.00016; Ho, Cora (Box 8)
  - Annual Reports 1993/94 Dept Stats, 1994; UA225.003.008.00017; Ho, Cora (Box 8)
  - Budget 1995/1996 Proposal and Actual, 1993 -- 1996; UA225.003.008.00018; Ho, Cora (Box 8)
  - HSL Information Services Annual Report, 1996; UA225.003.008.00019; Ho, Cora (Box 8)
  - Budget and Statistics 1996/97, 1995 -- 1996; UA225.003.008.00020; Ho, Cora (Box 8)
  - Budget 1998, 1997 -- 1998; UA225.003.008.00021; Ho, Cora (Box 8)
  - Budget 1997/98, 1997 -- 1998; UA225.003.008.00022; Ho, Cora (Box 8)
  - FY 1998/99, 1997 -- 1999; UA225.003.008.00023; Ho, Cora (Box 8)
  - Budget 1998/99, 1997 -- 1999; UA225.003.008.00024; Ho, Cora (Box 8)
  - Boston Library Consortium [1 of 2], 1977 -- 1982; UA225.003.008.00025; Ho, Cora (Box 8)
  - Boston Library consortium [2 of 2], 1976 -- 1982; UA225.003.008.00026; Ho, Cora (Box 8)
  - Announcements [1 of 3], 1992 -- 2003; UA225.003.009.00001 (Box 9)
  - Announcements [2 of 3], 2000 -- 2002; UA225.003.009.00002 (Box 9)
  - Announcements [3 of 3], 1990 -- 2003; UA225.003.009.00003 (Box 9)
  - Managing at Tufts @ Work [1 of 2], 1998; UA225.003.009.00004 (Box 9)
  - Managing at Tufts @ Work [2 of 2], 1998; UA225.003.009.00005 (Box 9)
  - 1987 Affiliated hospitals survey, UA225.003.009.00006 (Box 9)
  - Promotional material, 2013; UA225.003.009.00007; Hirsh Health Sciences Library (Box 9)
    Open for research.
  - NER004, 2000; UA225.003.010.00001
  - Performance, 2000; UA225.003.010.00002
  - Orientation, 2001; UA225.003.010.00003
  - HLC Teams 2000/01, 2000 -- 2001; UA225.003.010.00004
  - OPAL Mail, 1999 -- 2000; UA225.003.010.00006
  - MLANET, 2000; UA225.003.010.00007
  - Excel 1999/00, UA225.003.010.00009
  - Policy and Procedure, 1998 -- 1999; UA225.003.010.00011
  - HLC Team 00/01, 2000 -- 2001; UA225.003.010.00012
  - Rcycle 2 3/8/00, 1994 -- 2000; UA225.003.010.00013
  - Adm, 1996 -- 1999; UA225.003.010.00014
  - Back, 1999 -- 2002; UA225.003.010.00015
  - Admin 99, 1999; UA225.003.010.00016
  - ADMIN Administration, 2001; UA225.003.010.00017
  - clt 3, 1995 -- 1999; UA225.003.010.00018
  - CH Back up Temp, 1996 -- 2000; UA225.003.010.00019
  - More Files 3, 123, 1994 -- 1999; UA225.003.010.00020
  - More Files 1, 123, 1998 -- 1999; UA225.003.010.00021
  - PDQs, @Work, hsdbhandbook, 1997 -- 1999; UA225.003.010.00022
  - Rcycle 1, 1995 -- 2000; UA225.003.010.00023
- Slide library, 1893 -- 1998; UA225.004; 1.2 Linear Feet; 937 Digital Object(s)